 [
    {
    "question": "Who was responsible for the creation of the Night King?",
    "choice1": "The Lord of Light",
    "choice2": "The Children of the Forest",
    "choice3": "The Drowned God",
    "choice4": "The First Men",
    "answer": 2
},
{
    "question":
        "In the TV show, what was Hodor called before he got his tragic door-holding nickname?",
    "choice1": "Wylis",
    "choice2": "Horys",
    "choice3": "Myrys",
    "choice4": "Gladys",
    "answer": 1
},
{
    "question": "What is the Iron Bank’s representative, played by Mark Gatiss, called?",
    "choice1": "Quorin Halfhand",
    "choice2": "Xaro Xhoan Daxon",
    "choice3": "Howard from the Halifax",
    "choice4": "Tycho Nestoris",
    "answer": 4
},
{
    "question": "Dany’s dragons are (or were) called Drogon, Viserion and ____?",
    "choice1": "Dougal",
    "choice2": "Vhagar",
    "choice3": "Rhaegal",
    "choice4": "Balerion",
    "answer": 3
},
{
    "question": "Who said: 'I don’t plan on knitting by the fire while men fight for me'?",
    "choice1": "Lyanna Mormont",
    "choice2": "Sansa Stark",
    "choice3": "Ser Brienne of Tarth",
    "choice4": "Olenna Tyrell",
    "answer": 1
},
{
    "question": "Which of these characters is dead?",
    "choice1": "Jaqen H’Gar",
    "choice2": "Nymeria the direwolf",
    "choice3": "Hot Pie",
    "choice4": "Eddison Tollett",
    "answer": 4
},
{
    "question": "What is the name of the giant dragon-slaying crossbow that failed to protect King’s Landing?",
    "choice1": "Millipede",
    "choice2": "The 'You’re Making Me Very Cross(bow)'",
    "choice3": "Scorpion",
    "choice4": "Mantis",
    "answer": 3
},
{
    "question": "Where is the House of Black and White, the training temple of the Faceless Men?",
    "choice1": "Qarth",
    "choice2": "Braavos",
    "choice3": "Meereen",
    "choice4": "No one knows",
    "answer": 2
},
{
    "question": "What was the Red Keep’s chief mouser (RIP) called?",
    "choice1": "Ser Pounce",
    "choice2": "Maester Paw",
    "choice3": "Lady Claws, first of her name, breaker of mice, protector of the realm",
    "choice4": "The Bastard",
    "answer": 1
},
{
    "question": "What is the name of Arya’s sword?",
    "choice1": "Ice",
    "choice2": "Pointy",
    "choice3": "Fang",
    "choice4": "Needle",
    "answer": 4
},
{
    "question": "In which King’s Landing slum did Gendry grow up?",
    "choice1": "Flea Bottom",
    "choice2": "Rat Bottom",
    "choice3": "Rhaenys's Hill",
    "choice4": "Dragonpit",
    "answer": 1
},
{
    "question": "Who was Ned Stark’s predecessor as Robert Baratheon’s Hand?",
    "choice1": "Jaime Lannister",
    "choice2": "Jon Arryn",
    "choice3": "Tywin Lannister",
    "choice4": "Ser Jorah Mormont",
    "answer": 2
},
{
    "question": "Whose last words were: 'Give me something for the pain, and let me die'?",
    "choice1": "Stannis Baratheon",
    "choice2": "Hodor",
    "choice3": "Robert Baratheon",
    "choice4": "Walder Frey",
    "answer": 3
}
 ]
